# Kam Fai Ma

East York, ON M4W 0B3 holfitmf@hotmail.com +1 647 897 1011

I worked as a hospital pharmacist in Hong Kong for more than eight years since 2014. I am currently studying software engineering in Centennial College and I am looking forward to make contribution to the healthcare system from a different perspective.

## Personal Details

Highest Level of Education: Master's Degree

**Total years of experience:** 8

# Work Experience

### **Pharmacist**

HKSH Medical Group - Hong Kong August 2014 to December 2022

- 1. To participate in daily operation of the pharmacy
- 2. To perform and supervise the medication-use process
- 3. To deliver education/training and development programs for pharmacy staff and other health professionals

### **Pharmacy Intern**

Hong Kong Sanatorium & Hospital - Hong Kong January 2014 to June 2014

- 1. To participate in daily dispensing
- 2. To assist pharmacist to handle related duties

### **Pharmacy Intern**

Tuen Mun Hospital, Hospital Authority - Hong Kong July 2013 to December 2013

- 1. To participate in daily dispensing
- 2. To assist pharmacist to handle related duties

#### **Temporary Data Analyst**

Queen Mary Hospital, Hospital Authority - Hong Kong July 2012 to July 2012

1. To assist in data entry and data analysis of a survey on Accident and Emergency Service in Queen Mary Hospital

### Education

# **College diploma in Software Engineering**

Centennial College - Scarborough, ON September 2022 to Present

## **Master's degree in Pharmacy**

The Chinese University of Hong Kong - Hong Kong September 2014 to September 2016

# **Bachelor's in Pharmacy**

The University of Hong Kong - Hong Kong September 2010 to June 2013

### Skills

- Pharmacy Technician Experience
- Clinical Pharmacy Experience
- Hospital Experience
- Compounding Medications
- Supervising Experience
- Leadership
- Order Entry
- · Microsoft Office
- C#
- SQL
- Python
- HTML5
- JavaScript
- jQuery

## Languages

- Cantonese Fluent
- Mandarin Fluent
- English Fluent

## Certifications and Licenses

# **Certificate of Registration of Pharmacist (Hong Kong)**